Shah Sultanul Arefin

shahsarefin@gmail.com My Technical Blog and GITHUB

+14312939401

Winnipeg, MB, Canada

Availability: Up to 20-30 hours per week, including evening shifts.

PROFILE

Highly adaptable professional with diverse experience in customer service, food industry operations, web development, and IT technical support. Skilled in languages such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Python, and PostgreSQL also knows the basics of OsTickets, Active Directory, Microsoft Azure cloud service. Proficient using softwares like Teams or Slack. Currently Working in food industry while studying; Open to any job opportunities, both technical and non-technical, with strong capabilities in remote collaboration and excellent communication.

EXPERIENCE

RED LOBSTER, Winnipeg, MB Line Cook | May 2023-Present

- Expertise in high-pressure, fast-paced food industry environments.
- Excellence in food preparation, quality standards, and diverse menu items.
- Collaborative teamwork, enhanced customer service, evening shift readiness.

Chicken Delight, Winnipeg, MB Cook/Cashier | Jan 2023-April 2023

- Customer engagement, rapid issue resolution, cleanliness, organization.
- Effective food industry tasks handling, including preparation and presentation.

AppifyLab, Sylhet, Bangladesh Web Developer | Sep 2022- Nov 2022

- Collaborated remotely for web solutions, ensuring cross-browser compatibility.
- Designed and maintained user-friendly websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Web Development Diploma (IT Program) May 2023- Sep 2024 Red River College Polytechnic, Winnipeg, MB, Canada

BSc(Engg.) in Computer Science and Engineering Sep 2016 - Sep 2021 Metropolitan University, Sylhet, Bangladesh CGPA: 3.64 out of 4.00

SKILLS

- Technical Proficiency: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, PostgreSQL, Microsoft Office, OsTicket, Active Directory, Microsoft Azure, Teams, Slack.
- **Customer Interaction**: Inquiry handling, issue resolution, satisfaction enhancement.
- Adaptability & Flexibility: Rapid learning, task management, new challenge adaptation.
- **Industry Knowledge:** Food preparation, quality control, sanitation, presentation, web technologies.
- **Collaboration & Communication:** Independent and teamwork, remote coordination.
- **Analytical Abilities**: Problem-solving, creative solutions, complex instruction.
- Time & Organizational Skills: Efficiency, attention to detail, multitasking, 35 WPM typing.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Languages: Fluent in English and Bangla.
- Interests: Technology, Fitness, Reading, Continuous Learning and mentoring people.